{
    "id": "2ec0ead0058c4370acc5c93e14c12568",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I wouldn’t mind your coming late if you do not wake me ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is independent .............................................. his parents.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "of",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Sonia is the ........................................ of the two girls.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taller",
                "tallest"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you please move ..........................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "bit",
                "a bit"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There I saw his Mom ....................................... he said was away.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "This chair is quite cheap .......................................... $",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "for",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We do not sell things .................................... credit.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "on",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "As we labour, so shall we .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "reward",
                "be rewarded"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I’m ................................................ tired to attend the class.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has been absent ...................................... three days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}